>> Jem: 对于最终项目，我希望您创建交谈
&gt;&gt; Jem: For the final project
I want you to create a chat
使用 websockets 的机器人就是这样
bot using websockets, that's it.
我最喜欢的节目之一是英国大包
One of my favorite show was
the Great British Baking Show and
技术上的挑战，就像做个馅饼一样。
the technical challenge,
where it's just like make a pie.
没有其他的指示
And there's no other instructions.
你只需要知道怎么做或者查清楚
You just have to know how to do it or
look it up.
幸运的是我很友好我写了霍特 room.js
Fortunately, because I'm nice,
I wrote hotelroom.js,
是我昨晚在酒店房间里写的聊天机器人
which is a chat bot I wrote
last night in my hotel room.
所以请继续复制此存储库。
So, go ahead and clone this repo.
如果您运行节点应用程序，
And if you run node app,
我给你举个例子，当它运行时它的样子。
I'll give you example of what
it looks like when it's running.
我没完全清仓因为我想给你留个神秘感
I didn't fully flush it out because
I wanna leave some mystery for you.
但我可以像以前那样运行节点 app.js 。
But I can run node app.js
like we did before.
我们在 3000 口
We're running on port 3000.
我可以说当地的 3000 人
And I can say local hosts 3000.
嘿你怎么样
Hey, and how are you?
太聪明了
Smart, awesome.
其实都是这样回应的。
That's actually all it responds.
你好棒极了
Hi, awesome.
到目前为止都这么做了我会让你做其他的
That's all it does so far,
I'll let you build up the rest of that.
但现在我正在通过 Websocket 进行流式传输，因此
But right now I'm streaming
over a websocket, so
连接保持打开状态，服务器将持续 ping 通。
the connection stays open,
the server is pinging constantly.
只要保持联系就好了
Just keeping this connection alive.
我们会去查网络的
We'll check out the network.
第一，这一页。
First, this page.
看我们得到的是受欢迎的有效载荷每五秒左右
See that we get the welcome payload and
about every five seconds or so,
我们应该有个 ping 通了就能保持联系
we should get a ping coming through,
just keeping that connection alive.
如果没有的话，我看看我的代码，看看我做错了什么。
If not, I'll take a look at my code and
see what I did wrong.
但你说我们在客户上使用纯 websockets
But you say we're using on the client,
we're just using pure websockets.
我们不使用图书馆什么的
We're not using a library or
anything like that.
我们不使用 socket.io。
We're not using socket.io.
在服务器端，我正在使用 WS 库。
On the server side,
I'm using the WS library.
因此，在克隆该存储库之后，请确保您的 NPM 安装。
So make sure your NPM install
after you clone that repo.
而且，要让 websockets 在 EngineX公司工作，
And, to make websockets work in EngineX,
我们必须使用称为升级请求的内容。
we have to use what is known
as an upgrade request.
因此，在您的位置块中，必须添加标题升级 HD 升级，
So in your location block, you have
to add the header upgrade HD upgrade,
以及连接类型升级。
and the connection type upgrade.
因为 Web 套接字比常规连接更好。
Because web sockets are better
than regular connection.
所以这是升级如果你愿意的话
So it's an upgrade, if you will.
这将允许 Web 套接字流到节点应用程序。
And that will allow the websockets to
stream through to your node application.
剩下的我就留给你了
The rest I will leave up to you for now.
在我们分手之前还有什么问题吗
Is there any questions
before we break fully?
有些人看起来很困惑
Some of you look confused.
>> 演讲者 2: 目标是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What's the goal?
总体目标是什么 ?
What's the overarching goal?
>> Jem: 要将 Websocket 连接流式方法构建到服务器中。
&gt;&gt; Jem: To build a websocket connection
streaming through to your server.
>> 演讲者 3: 要做什么，再说一次。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: To what, say it again.
>> Jem: 我们正在建立一个聊天机器人。
&gt;&gt; Jem: We're building a chat bot.
我说 bot bot ， bot bot.
Well, I say chat bot but, chat bot.
太傻了
It's pretty dumb.
但我们使用的是 Websocket 连接，而不仅仅是纯 TCP 连接。
But we're using a websocket connection
rather than just a pure TCP connection.
所以我们不会那样做。
So we're not doing that back and forth.
这只是一个单一的联系。
It's just one single connection.
这意味着您需要将其连接到客户机中，
So that means you need to
connect it in the client,
您需要将其路由到您的服务器以进入您的 EngineX 配置。
you need to route it through to your
server into your EngineX configuration.
从 EngineX ，它需要将该 Websocket 路由到 Express 应用程序。
From EngineX it needs a route that
websocket to your Express application.
Express 应用程序需要处理该 Websocket 和
And the Express application needs
to handle that websocket and
然后再从隧道回回来
then respond back all the way
back through the tunnel.
我没让它硬了
See, I wasn't making it hard,
我本来要把这些都放在一个子域上但我不想让你太努力
I was gonna make this all on a subdomain,
but I didn't wanna push you too hard.
对于子域上可以执行的奖励积分。
For bonus points you
can do on a subdomain.
> > 演讲者 3: 我们要把我们所得到的东西都炸掉
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We're just gonna blow
away what we've got so far and easier.
>> Jem: 如果喜欢。
&gt;&gt; Jem: If you like.
另一个选项是您可以添加其他位置块，并且
Another option is you can add
a different location block and
将流量路由到其他节点应用程序。
route your traffic to just
a different node application.
带 PMC 的 Cuz ，我们可以运行 50 个节点应用程序。
Cuz with PMC, we can run 50 node
applications if we want to.
完全符合你的要求
Totally up to you.
这与自由格式的技术部分相似，因此您可以使其正常工作。
This is like the technical portion of
the free form so you can get it working.
如果你想点暗示把雷波克隆到你的本地机器上
And if you want a few hints,
clone the repo to your local machine,
运行节点 app.js。
run node app.js.
然后去当地的 3000 台主机上
And then go to local host
3000 on your local machine,
它会帮助您在放置服务器之前进行调试。
and it'll help you debug
before you put on the server.